Stop barking. Come.
Hello! Stop barking.
Do it slowly. Slowly.
All total 97,000 won.
I just told you to put in 3,000 worth.
What?
I said put in only 3,000 worth.
I told you before to just put
in 3,000 worth.
Aigoo. Did you mess it up
again, grandfather?
I apologize, Customer!
This grandfather is a little
hard of hearing.
I told you if you wanted to
do this job,
you should wear your
hearing aid, okay?
Give it to me. I'll do it.
I will!
It's fine. It's fine.
I'll need it anyway.
Just give me the bill.
Okay. If you were in Riga (Latvia)
and filled this car with diesel,
it might cost you $800.
Really?
I'm sorry.
Thank you.
Take care!
Wait! Your water!
Good. Thank you.
I mean, they agreed to sign the
contract last week.
Now they're dragging their feet
and saying weird things,
so they must be looking around.
=Tunnel ahead. Please drive
safely.=
If they signed the contract,
I was going to buy you a bag.
Wait until next time.
=You shouldn't be wasting
your money.=
=Just think about what to
buy Su Jin for her birthday
besides a puppy.=
=Just think about what to
buy Su Jin for her birthday
besides a puppy.=
Our place is too small for a dog.
And they shed too much.
=Oh, I don't know.
What time will you be here?=
I have to take the car into the
garage first.
The horn doesn't work.
=So, when will you be home?=
About 5:59 or so?
I bought the cake.
Se Hyeon, I'll be home soon!
=Okay.=
Yes, Sir.
I am Lee Jeong Su with the
Hado Agency. I'm driving
now, so please go ahead.
=I told you that I needed
10 cars.=
=But it turns out I'm a little
short of funds.=
=I've decided to buy 8. Can you
include 3 fire extinguishers?=
Sir, my life's motto is all about
3 things.
Offer more. Deliver more.
Discount more.
Of course we can.
Especially since it affects
children's safety.
=You're very refreshing. Then
I'll buy 8. Let's sign the contract
on Monday.=
Thank you, Sir. I will continue
to work hard.
=So, what is the total cost?=
I was a liberal arts major, so
my math skills aren't very good.
I'll stop the car after this tunnel
and figure it out.
Then I'll call you right back.
=Okay, let's do that.=
I'll call you back in a minute.
Thank you.
What happened?
Hello?
=Dialing emergency 119.=
=This is 119. What's your
emergency?
Yes. The tunnel has collapsed
here and I'm trapped inside.
This is in...
=Sir, I can't hear you well.
Please speak louder.=
- Okay. I'm here in...
=Hello?=
- The tunnel collapsed here.
Tunnel! Tunnel collapse.
Tunnel. Tunnel.
=Do you mean there are rocks
in the tunnel?=
I said the tunnel collapsed.
Just now.
=It collapsed?=
Yes. Please come quickly.
=Which tunnel are you
talking about?=
=Hello?=
- Hello?
=Sir, which tunnel are you
talking about?=
=Hello? Hello, Sir?=
This is Hado Tunnel!
Hado Tunnel!
=Hado Tunnel?=
- Yes.
=The Hado Tunnel on Highway
18, is that right?=
That's right.
It's collapsed inside and I'm
trapped in here.
Hello? Hello?
=This is 119 headquarters.=
=Did you say the tunnel has
collapsed around your car?=
I said the tunnel collapsed...
There are rocks on top of me
and rocks all around.
=So how bad does the collapse
seem?=
Very serious. It's completely
caved in.
Stop asking. Can't you just
come quickly?
=Yes, yes. Sir, what is your
name?=
Lee Jeong Su. Lee Jeong Su.
I'm with the Hado Kia Agency.
Lee Jeong Su.
=Okay.=
How long will it be?
=Lee Jeong Su. Okay. If there's
no traffic, they should be there
in 5 minutes.=
Hello? Mister.
=Please wait in a safe place.=
Hello?
Safe place? What bullshit.
If he'd only put in $30 worth
of gas,
I would have made it through
this tunnel. Seriously.
-=119 Rescue Team=-
=How is the tunnel?=
=What?=
Dear viewers, there has been
another disaster in our country.
This time, a tunnel.
Just a month after opening, a
tunnel has tragically collapsed.
Now just as you all can see,
the mountain above the tunnel
has completely collapsed.
There is a slide at the area of
construction above the tunnel.
The entrance to the north side
of the tunnel is completely
blocked.
From the south entrance, it
looks as if there was an attack.
Everything is pitch-black
from the dust.
Because of the new construction,
there was almost no traffic
through the Hado Tunnel.
But the first call made to 119
was made from someone inside
the tunnel.
Inside the collapsed tunnel,
at least one person has been
trapped.
Consideration is being given as
to how to approach the incident.
The identity of the person in the
tunnel is now confirmed.
He is a 38-year-old car salesman
from Hado.
Once again.
The first call from the Hado
Tunnel came from a 38-year-old
man.
The first call from the Hado
Tunnel came from a 38-year-old
man.
He has been identified as
Lee Jeong Su.
We have determined the man
trapped in the collapsed tunnel
is Lee Jeong Su.
Hello?
=Hello? Is this Lee Jeong Su?=
Yes.
=You're the Lee Jeong Su who's
trapped in the tunnel, right?=
Yes, have you arrived?
=Hurry, connect us!=
=I am SNC reporter,
Jo Yang Cheol.=
Lee Jeong Su,
=It's okay with you if we
broadcast this interview, right?=
=Broadcasting this will be
helpful in trying to save you.=
-=Exclusive phone interview
with survivor. News flash.=-
The rescue work has already
begun,
but it may take a long time
due to the size of the slide.
=Do you have any food in there
with you?=
You said it may take a long
time.
What does that mean?
=You mean the rescue team
hasn't told you the plan?=
Just how long a period of time
are you talking about?
They can't get me out of here
immediately?
=It seems they haven't
explained the situation to you.=
=They aren't sure about the
Hado side,=
=but the Seoul side has
completely collapsed.=
=The entrance is totally
destroyed.=
=Lee Jeong Su, what is your
mood right now?=
Hey! Where the hell is that
call from?
It seems like the staging area.
Then you should stop it, Kid!
He'll deplete his battery.
Hey, hey, hey you! Hurry and
hang up the phone!
If you keep this up, his phone
will go dead!
But they're broadcasting live.
It will end soon. Very soon.
This guy is really pissing me off.
Please go ahead.
=Yes, Lee Jeong Su.=
Hang that up right now!
What do you think you're doing?
What the hell are you all doing?
The victim's phone has now
been disconnected.
=We will sort out the situation
and report again.=
Who the hell are you? You just
screwed up a live broadcast!
Did you not see the story that
was just on the air?
Reporters, right now is your
story more important or is a
life more important?
What?
You can't answer a simple
question?
If because of you,
that person's phone battery
goes dead,
because of being isolated,
he will become anxious with
fast heartbeat and breathing
difficulty!
Because of inadequate oxygen,
his blood flow will slow down!
Due to long-term lack of energy
his heart will stop beating!
What then, Mr. Reporter?
Will you take responsibility?
That's for Lee Jeong Su...
This is a lifeline! A lifeline!
If you call him again,
you will be in violation of article
18 of the media responsibility law.
Please. Don't call him.
Why is this van still parked here?
Get it out of here! Right now!
Hey! Why are you letting
cars come in here?
Can't you keep them out of here?
Can't you even restrict access
here?
Our car shouldn't even be here!
They didn't stop and just drove
right through.
Sang Hun.
Yes.
Charge this.
Okay.
Good job. It's true that
knowledge is power.
There was nothing they
could say.
What was that media law you
just mentioned?
Just something I threw out.
It's not real?
Those reporters didn't say
anything.
It looks like they weren't even
sure about it.
Kid, go check the rescue
regulations.
-=1. Definition of collapse.=-
There aren't any instructions
in here?
It's in English and still being
translated.
Translate this into English
and return it to them.
Captain, Lee Jeong Su called.
Hey, close them. Close them.
Hello, Lee Jeong Su. I'm the
rescue team captain, Kim Dae
Gyeong.
=Why do you never answer
the phone?=
What?
=What are you all doing?=
=Didn't you just say you
would rescue me quickly?=
=Is it different than that?=
Lee Jeong Su, calm down and
listen to me.
=How can you tell me to
calm down?=
Hurry and explain this to me.
What's going on out there now?
Just tell me the truth!
=Lee Jeong Su, if you're like
this, I can't talk to you.=
Hey, you son of a bitch!
Then who can I talk to?
=Then give someone else the
phone! Let me talk to the
person in charge!=
Lee Jeong Su, I am the person
in charge. You need to listen.
Son of a bitch, then hurry up.
=Lee Jeong Su, listen to what
I say.=
=First, Lee Jeong Su, you have
to calm down.=
I am... right now I'm calm.
Just hurry and tell me.
Then you need to do this. Lee
Jeong Su, take a deep breath.
Just follow me and take a deep
breath.
I'm already breathing so just
tell me.
=I'm sorry. I am the rescue
leader, Kim Dae Gyeong.=
Lee Jeong Su, how much charge
is left on your phone battery?
It's at 78%. Why? Why are you
asking that?
=Yes. Well, I'm going to tell
you the truth now.=
=First of all, this situation is
not very simple.=
=Of course, we will definitely
rescue you.=
But it's probably going to take
some time is what I'm saying.
The Minister wants to come.
Minister?
Lee Jeong Su, do you have any
water in the car?
Water or drinks,
or any food?
Hello? Hello? Lee Jeong Su?
Come on, come on.
Get it together.
Lee Jeong Su, do you have any
water? Water?
Please answer me. Lee Jeong Su?
I have 2 bottles of water and
a cake.
Okay. How many milliliters?
They're small, 500 mL and a
cream cake.
The cake won't last a long time.
You should probably eat that
quickly.
And the water, the water...
That's very important.
=I think you'll have to make it
last about 7 days.=
=Mark it. Be sure to drink as
much as possible.=
=And drink without it touching
your lips,=
=so the water won't become
polluted.=
Wait.
=You understand, right?=
So you mean, I'll have to be
here for a week?
You will be rescued before you
drink all that water.
Lee Jeong Su, you understand
what I explained to you about
the water, right?
Don't touch my mouth.
Divide it to last for one week.
Very good. You remembered
it correctly.
Lee Jeong Su, do you happen
to know your present position?
In other words, about how far
are you from the tunnel entrance?
=This is very important for
the rescue.=
Oh, yes. I was quite far into it.
There's a ventilation fan that
fell on top of me.
What? Ventilation fan?
There's a fan on top of the car?
Hey. Hurry and get the plans.
Okay. A ventilation fan on the
car is very important information.
Go over there.
Okay. We're looking at the
diagrams, so hold on a moment.
We have the plans now.
You just tore them.
=Look, there's no problem.=
Could you see the exit when
you entered the tunnel?
=No. I couldn't see it.=
Okay.
=There isn't anything else?=
I went around the bend. After
that, I drove inside.
I can't remember.
Okay. Fine. Lee Jeong Su.
From now on at 12:00,
we'll contact you.
But for today,
turn your phone off immediately.
Who did you say you are again?
=Yes. Kim Dae Gyeong, rescue
team leader.=
Please tell me the truth.
Can you save me?
We have saved many people
in this country.
You'll be out of there very soon.
You and I will meet on that day.
Hey. Put it there. Geez.
Five ventilation fans and Lee
Jeong Su is under one of them.
Okay. Okay. Okay.
Honey. Honey.
=Honey, are you okay?
Are you injured?=
I'm okay.
I'm really okay. I'll get out.
They told me it will be about
one week from now.
Don't worry. Don't cry.
I'll get out of here very soon.
You should save your battery.
Just talk to me for a minute.
Su Jin. Does Su Jin know?
I told her you were busy at
work and couldn't come home.
Do you want to talk to her?
Yes. Put her on.
Su Jin. Daddy bought your cake
and was bringing it home.
But something happened and I
can't come. I'm sorry.
Daddy, I'm going to grandma's
house. Can you come there?
I want to get my cake and my
the gift. My puppy.
Right. Daddy will buy the
puppy and then come.
=Really? Mom! Daddy said he'll
come after he buys the puppy!=
=I'm taking Su Jin to my mom's
house and then I'll come there.=
No, no, no. Just stay there.
=I'm coming.=
Okay.
The tunnel length is 1.9 km.
Lee Jeong Su's position
is in one of the 5 areas marked
here.
The lowest place is more than
100 meters deep and there are
many rocks.
So going from the south
entrance seems the most
effective method.
After we confirm the situation
tomorrow, we will decide
whether we begin there.
The implementation of rescue
efforts should be discussed with
experts.
Everyone must treat this as
if it were their own family,
and put in their best effort.
Also, there is construction
nearby for a second Hado tunnel.
That will be suspended for now.
There's another tunnel here?
Yes. It's currently under
construction nearby.
They were working on the
final section.
Will the second tunnel in the
area also be affected?
Because the opening of the new
Hado city is not far away,
it must be completed as soon
as possible.
Consult the experts and then
get started.
Let's do all that we can.
Will that be enough now?
Are there enough here now?
Yes.
Wait, wait, wait! We have to
change cards. Just a moment.
Such a headache.
Here we go! The people in
front, crouch down a bit.
Get a bit lower.
Crouch down a bit lower.
You're blocking our view!
Okay. Thank you!
Let's go. Let's go.
Okay.
Send them in now! Send them!
We don't want the drones to
hit anyone!
Please don't get too close!
What the hell's going on?
Okay.
What? What happened?
They lost the signal.
It's not very far from here.
They have a range of 5 km.
If the signal is weak, then the
range will be shorter.
There must be a lot of iron ore
in there.
If wireless doesn't work,
can't you use wired ones?
This is the only type of device
I have.
But if you want to get through
there,
we have some at the factory.
Okay. Then call a courier to
deliver them quickly.
What are you doing?
Where's your factory?
Ontario. In America.
Aigoo.
Hey. You stay here.
Can you do it alone?
Yes.
The whole thing is collapsed.
Your wife is on the phone!
Tell her I'll call her back.
And you, don't honk that horn.
Got it?
I'm sorry!
Idiot.
Has he gone crazy?
What?
Sorry, I pressed it by accident.
Sorry.
Captain!
Lee Jeong Su is on the phone!
Yes, Lee Jeong Su.
Is there someone around here?
=What?=
I think I just heard a car horn
honk twice.
=Really?=
Oh! I heard it again! Again!
That... is me.
He can hear that?
I just heard the horn honk
5 times again.
Yes, yes! Lee Jeong Su.
We might see you sooner than
we expected.
=Really?=
=Thank you! Thank you!=
Lee Jeong Su, get down in
your car immediately!
=Protect yourself!=
-=Hado Tunnel - Safe and
Happy Construction=-
The phone! Phone! Phone!
Captain! Captain!
Captain, are you all right?
Give me a phone!
You can't come in! You can't!
Hello? Lee Jeong Su!
Can you hear me? Can you hear?
I hear you.
=Are you okay?=
It collapsed a bit more,
but I'm okay.
There was just another major
collapse at the entrance!
=I'm sorry.=
It says ventilation fan #3.
=Number 3. Number 3.=
Your wife...
What did you say?
=It looks like your wife has
come here.=
=Do you want to talk to her?=
Yes. Put her on. Put her on.
=Oppa, are you okay?=
Did you have breakfast?
You're asking me that now?
=I'm really fine.=
I'll call you again later.
Remember to eat breakfast.
Yesterday at 8:30 a.m.,
the rescue team was able to
accurately locate Lee Jeong Su's
position.
From the surface, we plan to
drill about 180 meters down,
to open a rescue channel
towards Lee Jeong Su.
We also intend to enter from
the south entrance.
1. Top (vertical) excavation.
2-Track method.
Underground Location.
Lee Jeong Su (38)
1. Top (vertical) excavation.
2-Track method.
Underground Location.
Lee Jeong Su (38)
1. Top (vertical) excavation.
2-Track method.
Underground Location.
Lee Jeong Su (38)
According to the President's
orders,
we will use all means possible
in order to save Lee Jeong Su.
Therefore, our rescue team feels
using a 2-track method
will be the fastest way to
carry out the rescue.
Our government will do its best.
This is Lee Jeong Su's wife.
Aigoo. Aigoo.
I will rely on you.
They want to take a photo.
Please look this way.
Wait a moment.
1. 2. 3.
-=3 days after collapse=-
8. 7. 6. 5. 4. 3. 2. 1. Ding!
10. 9. 8...
-=Hado Kia Agency
Lee Jeong Su=-
-=Drying Agent=-
-=Glass Cleaner=-
Who's there?
Mutt!
Get!
Why are you here?
Hello? Is someone out there?
I'm over here.
Are you hurt?
I'm pinned down.
Please help me!
Wait a moment.
Ajussi!
You're not leaving are you?
Please don't leave me!
I'm not going anywhere. Wait.
I'm stuck here too.
-=Rescue Captain, there is
also a girl in here.=-
I'm not going anywhere. Wait.
I'm stuck here too.
-=Rescue Captain, there is
also a girl in here.=-
I'm coming, so wait just a bit.
Ajussi, you're coming aren't you?
Yes, I'm coming. Hang on.
Did something happen?
It's okay. I'm coming. It's fine.
I'm fine. Nothing happened.
It's all right.
I'm on my way.
That hurts.
Almost there.
Mutt.
You're in here.
I... I can't move.
I need to get in there first.
Okay.
You need to move.
I'll try to move some of the
rocks and see.
I'm sorry. It's very tight here.
It won't even budge.
Are you okay?
Ajussi, the light.
The light.
Otherwise I'm fine.
But my ribs hurt a bit.
Your ribs?
Should I try to move the
chair back?
I don't think it will move.
How long have we been
trapped in here?
I think about 2 days and
7 hours.
What's going to happen to us?
Will we die?
No. Right now, all of South
Korea is out there.
They're doing everything they
can to rescue us.
Is that true?
Of course.
Thank goodness.
So when are we going to get out?
Probably...
When I talked to them on
the phone,
they said it would probably
take a few days.
He doesn't have any injuries?
I don't think so.
He still seems pretty lively.
But, what kind of collar is this?
It's a bark-control collar.
Tangie. Tangie?
Tangie, come here.
Tangie.
Do you... I'm sorry.
What?
Do you have any water?
Water?
I have some in my car.
I'll go get it.
Enough?
A little... a little more.
It's not good to drink very
much all of a sudden.
Just drink a little bit to get
your throat moist.
That's fine.
Ajussi.
Yes.
Could you give Tangie a bit?
Just pour a little in your hands.
Okay. Of course.
Tangie, come here.
Ajussi will give you a drink.
No, no. You can't come
that way.
Come this way.
Tangie, come here.
Right.
Here.
Ajussi.
That's good.
Can you help me look for
my phone?
It's all broken. It won't turn on.
I'm sorry to trouble you again.
What?
Could I use your phone
for a moment?
I need to make a call.
Okay.
I'll help you.
Mom, it's me. Mi Na.
Yes.
What should I do?
Mom.
I'm... trapped inside a tunnel.
Yes. Yes.
No. I'm not alone.
I'm here with another man.
Don't worry.
I'll be able to get out in a few
days.
Yes.
Mom, I miss you.
But Mom, I can't talk very long.
We have to save the battery.
And Mom, would you call
my work for me?
Explain everything to them.
Mom, don't cry.
I'm okay.
Ajussi, we're going to be out
in a few days, right?
Yes. Of course.
Mom, we'll be out of here
within a week.
Tell them I'll be able to attend
the new staff training.
Also...
your car is completely wrecked.
I'm sorry, Mom.
Yes. I'll call you again later.
Yes.
Ajussi.
My Mom wants to talk to you.
What?
Me?
Yes, I'm Lee Jeong Su with
the Kia Hado Agency.
Hello.
Yes.
I'll take good care of Mi Na.
I'll bring her out of here.
Don't worry.
Yes. We have water.
She just drank a lot of water.
Yes. Yes. Thank you.
Goodbye. Yes.
Mi Na, I brought these socks.
I was going to let you wear
them.
You can use them to wipe
all your tears if you cry.
Okay.
Aigoo. Does it hurt?
This side is dirty. Is it okay?
Yes, it's fine.
-=Clear Water Motel=-
Enjoy your meal.
Thank you.
We reserved a heated room
for you.
This is the key and the invoice.
Thank you.
The room should have been
covered,
but there's a lot of red tape.
Hold onto the invoice and it
can be handled later.
Okay.
=According to reports, even in
a life-threatening situation,
Lee Jeong Su,=
=According to reports, even in
a life-threatening situation,
Lee Jeong Su,=
=shared his water with others.=
=In that situation, Lee Jeong Su
has not lost his humanity.=
=Let's all pray that he is able
to come out safe and sound.=
=Thank you all for watching.=
Ajussi, what do you do?
My career?
Yes.
I'm a salesman at the Hado
Kia agency.
=This is FM 94.2.=
It works.
=Classical music channel.=
Classical. Classical.
It's not bad. I don't mind
classical music.
Do you like classical music?
I heard it for the first time after
I graduated from high school.
Are you all right?
I'm fine.
Ajussi, I'm going to sleep for
a while.
Okay. I'll go back to my car.
If you need anything, call me.
And, there's this.
Here is the button.
Keep this light off or the
battery will die.
I'll leave it on until you
get back to your car.
Thank you.
It was nice to meet you.
Mi Na, turn on the light!
I'm sorry. Tangie is biting
the flashlight.
Tangie, let go.
Tangie, that little son of a bitch.
That son of a bitch.
I'm home. I'm back home.
Daddy will be out of here
very soon.
We can share that.
What?
You son of a bitch!
Son of a bitch!
Damn it!
That was my Su Jin's cake!
You son of a bitch. Damn you!
Ajussi, is something wrong?
No. I was dreaming. Dreaming.
Eat some of this.
Aigoo. That's enough!
Eat it while it's hot.
You should rest.
You're all working so hard to
save my husband.
Thank you.
I should do something.
Enjoy your food!
Let me get you some...
That's okay. That's okay.
It's fine. It's fine.
Ajussi.
Ajussi, come here.
Okay!
Ajussi, will it take them a long
time to get here?
They'll come for us very soon.
Just wait a little longer.
He said they're definitely
coming.
Mi Na, are you okay?
My ribs hurt so it's hard to
breathe.
Just hold on a little longer.
I'll go call them.
Ajussi, I'm sorry, but do you
have any water?
I'm sorry, but I drank it all.
Wait, Mi Na. I'll go get some
for you.
Wait a moment.
Okay. There's a little bit left.
Tangie, you'd better stay away.
You know what this is, right?
Mi Na. Mi Na?
Mi Na.
What's wrong? Don't scare me.
Mi Na, I brought water.
Mi Na.
Hold on. I'll help you move
back.
Mi Na, I'm sorry.
Yesterday, a victim in the Hado
Tunnel died.
An investigation is underway
into the cause for the collapse.
A lot of information is emerging
regarding shoddy construction.
Two-thirds of our 121 tunnels
were recently inspected.
More than 78 tunnels are not up
to standards, which is causing
widespread concern.
More than 78 tunnels are not up
to standards, which is causing
widespread concern.
During construction of a tunnel,
in order to prevent the collapse
of the rock,
During construction of a tunnel,
in order to prevent the collapse
of the rock,
During construction of a tunnel,
in order to prevent the collapse
of the rock,
each section should have 10
anchor bolts.
But it's not visible from the
outside, so no one does. Who's
going to know?
But it's not visible from the
outside, so no one does. Who's
going to know?
But it's not visible from the
outside, so no one does. Who's
going to know?
In Korea, there's not one company
that follows FM standards.
That's just tempting fate,
isn't that right?
Didn't you say you'd rescue me
before I drank all the water?
=Yes. I'm sorry.=
Truthfully, you can't do it, right?
No. We will. I will get you out.
Just wait a while longer.
We will definitely get in there.
=You're saving urine in the
empty bottles, right?=
Urine is sterile, so you can
drink it.
Did you drink it before?
=I'm sorry. I never have.=
-=9 days after collapse=-
Go away, brat.
What is that?
Where did this come from?
You ate my cake last time.
Two for me. One for you.
My nose is bigger than yours,
so I get four.
You get two.
Understand?
Okay, Tangie. Eat up.
Eat. Eat. It's okay. Relax.
It's okay. Relax.
Your food needs seasoning.
Don't look. Don't look.
Don't look. Look away.
Here it is.
I absolutely won't let you
open this.
Should I take this off?
Wow. This is something.
Bad dog.
Be still. It has a button.
Is this nice?
You need to learn to bury it
like a cat does.
Who do you think is going to
clean up after you?
Who will pick it up?
There's no way I could
drink your urine.
Yes.
How is the digging progressing?
=Because it's relatively hard,
it's been going slowly.=
=Within 10 days we should
surely be through.=
=Plus, we have to shore up the
tunnel entrance properly.=
=We should start digging today.=
22. 23. 24.
24. 10.
Lee Jeong Su, I... drank urine.
Why would you drink urine?
I had never done it, so I felt
bad telling you to do it.
Also... don't drink it right away.
Let it cool first. That helps.
You've given me a lot of
encouragement. Thank you.
Do you want some?
Tangie, this is orange juice.
My body can squeeze out
orange juice.
That's weird, right?
Honey, I found water.
Drinking water.
=It tasted sweet.=
=Sweet water?=
=Don't be worrying about me.=
=You must eat properly, okay?=
=Okay. I'll call you later.=
Are you doing okay?
I heard you drank urine.
How much did you drink?
Seriously, he shouldn't have
told you.
It was a paper cup.
Not like this one...
About the size of that one.
Do you want a drink?
Drink it yourself.
=As our audience friends know,=
=the only radio station Lee
Jeong Su can receive=
=in the tunnel is our station.=
=If the rescue team loses
contact with him before the
rescue,=
=we will broadcast at 12:00=
=for 5 minutes to pass the
rescue news to Lee Jeong Su.=
=We hope everyone can
understand.=
This is the top of the tunnel
structure.
It came out this morning.
If we keep drilling overnight,
we expect to reach the
underground tunnel tomorrow.
Lee Jeong Su will be out soon!
Thank you. Thank you.
-=Mom: Mom will be bringing
Dad over there soon.=-
-=Su Jin: And the puppy?=-
Seonbae.
We think it will be soon.
Let's go.
I guess I fell asleep.
I'm so tired.
Wow. That's too bad.
One more day and he'd break
the record.
The last record was 17 days.
Then Mr. Reporter, would you
like to try for the record?
Everyone move aside!
How can you block this area?
That guy is really...
Why would we need to break
the record?
Who knows?
=Keep watching up above.=
Okay.
=If anything starts to come
through,=
=just get away quickly.=
=It's only 0.6 meter around,
so you don't have to move much.=
Thank you. Then I'll see you
soon.
It seems like it will come
through here.
We'll be out soon.
Higher, higher, higher!
This is a ventilation fan blade...
and this is asphalt.
Then we must be in the tunnel,
right?
That's right.
We've reached the bottom.
Don't speak too soon.
But we found broken pieces of
the ventilation fan.
Bring over the blueprints.
Yes, here we go.
They're acting kind of strange.
Look and see what's going on.
Lee Jeong Su, did you...
see the drill come through?
I didn't see it.
Are the 2 ventilation fans still
intact?
Yes. Why?
After I confirm things, I'll
call you back.
Wait!
What is this?
This film was taken when the
tunnel was opened.
Watch.
There are several fans showing.
There should be 7.
One is missing.
How is that possible?
There are six. Six.
Damn it! This is worthless!
Worthless!
Check it again.
One. Two. Three. Four.
Five. Six...
We thought there were 7, so we
thought No. 3 was right here.
Actually, it's here.
Then these blueprints are wrong?
Does that make any sense?
It doesn't.
Captain, the fan installation
master said there should be 12.
The team installed one for
every two, in 6 places.
It was the wrong place.
Really?
Yes.
You mean they worked 17 days
for nothing?
Isn't that Lee Jeong Su's wife?
So how far is it from
Lee Jeong Su now?
About 150 meters.
He won't be able to move
that far.
Then, we're going to have
to drill again?
When will you get through?
=I'm sorry.=
What?
=We drilled in the wrong place.=
What do you mean by that?
We got the wrong location and
drilled in the wrong place.
How can it be wrong?
=I'm really sorry.=
If that's the case, then what
should I do?
=First, we will restart the
tunnel intersection project.=
And then?
=We'll start drilling all over
again.=
Starting over?
=We will go as fast as we can.=
=Oppa, are you okay?=
Oppa. What's wrong?
I can't breathe.
Try to calm down and I'll find a
doctor.
I need some help here! He's
acting strange. Hurry!
No, no, no. My battery is going.
Se Hyeon, this is my last call.
Se Hyeon, my battery is dead.
=Give the phone to Su Jin.=
Oppa, Su Jin isn't here.
Oppa! Oppa, be strong.
I can't stay here.
=Oppa!=
Se Hyeon, I can't hold on.
=You have to stay strong, Oppa!=
=Just hold on.=
Why do you keep telling me
to be strong?
I said I can't do it.
Honey. Hello? Hello?
Tell me. Tell me, Oppa.
Take good care of Su Jin and
live your life well.
What are you saying?
Se Hyeon, I'm sorry.
I just can't go on.
I really can't go on.
Is that so? Then just do that.
Just go ahead and die. Die!
But... if you die,
Su Jin and I will die too!
Oppa, if you die then all of us
will die! Understand?
I'm not threatening you.
=Otherwise, just keep going.=
Don't talk about dying or
things like that, okay?
You have to keep holding on.
You have to live.
Please just live, okay? Please!
What now? What now?
Madam! Hey! Hurry, hurry!
Call an ambulance!
I'm asking why the snow
blowers aren't here yet!
=Right now they're cleaning
roads in town.=
We don't have any extra
machines to send there.
Shouldn't this place be top
priority?
There have been more than 50
car accidents in the past 2 days.
There was a fatal accident
yesterday.
We're really too busy to die.
I know this isn't good to say,
=but isn't it only one person?=
That person... that one person...
is still alive!
Do you know how long he's
been waiting?
Chief, I'm begging you.
Please send us one snow-
blowing machine!
Is Lee Jeong Su is still alive?
The miners in Chile were
rescued on the 69th day.
=23 days after collapse=
The miners in Chile were
rescued on the 69th day.
=23 days after collapse=
But that involved 33 people.
Additionally, their food supply
was not a problem.
In a case like this without
any food,
the longest record of survival
is 19 days.
And with the extremely
disturbing cold,
on top of any injuries, it would
be even more difficult, right?
I can see that you're
pessimistic, right?
There are always variables,
so we can't jump to conclusions.
Yes.
Today, is Lee Jeong Su's 23rd
day of isolation.
Contact was lost one week ago.
During this time, we don't know
what might have happened to
Lee Jeong Su.
We should not be too hasty
in coming to conclusions,
and consider carefully.
We are more willing to believe
in hope rather than statistics.
=This is a letter from
Lee Jeong Su's wife.=
="Recently, Su Jin said living is
too hard."=
="Why would Su Jin say such
a thing at her age?"=
="She doesn't like studying in
kindergarten."=
="Learning addition and
subtraction is too hard?"=
="It seems she might be good
at your major in liberal arts."=
="Today she said her happiest
time was when she was inside
my tummy."=
="I didn't know whether to laugh
or cry when she said she wanted
to get back inside..."=
="...but she had gotten
too big..."=
=Today, we're going to play a
song that's not usual for our
station.=
=Classical music fans may be
surprised, but please forgive us.=
=Lee Jeong Su, please listen.=
From here on, the tunnel
intersection rescue work,
how is it progressing?
We are about 200 meters away
from Lee Jeong Su's location.
If we go forward 15 meters
a day, we will reach him in
15 days.
After the failure of vertical drilling
at nearly 9 days from the south...
Why did they call us here?
What are they doing?
The 2nd tunnel project has
been stalled for nearly 25 days.
Every day we're losing about
$1.5 million.
Our loss to date has exceeded
$50 million.
Why are you unable to proceed
with the 2nd tunnel?
We need to do blasting with
dynamite, so it's possible
Lee Jeong Su's location would
be impacted.
Then, how much longer do we
have to wait?
Honestly, I came here today
just to look you all in the eyes.
Last time, because of a lizard,
you must remember how the
tunneling was interrupted.
Do you know how much damage
was done to the national economy?
Just because of some lizard?
Hey. Excuse me, but Lee Jeong
Su is not a lizard. He's a person.
Right now, trapped in that
tunnel is not a reptile. It's a
person. A person.
I didn't mean anything by
what I said.
Yes. Although that's how it is,
I feel like you keep forgetting
this fact.
Right now, a person is trapped
in there. A person.
Go rest! I'll do it.
How must longer are we doing
this?
I know. What is all this just
to dig out a corpse?
Hey, how can you say
something like that?
Everyone keeps saying there's
no hope.
They all think it but don't say it.
Honestly, team leader, that's
what you think too, isn't it?
No. Quit saying that kind of thing.
Go back to work.
Yes, yes.
Team leader! Team leader!
Minister, someone was just
killed at the rescue site.
See? I knew that would happen.
Mom, she's wearing you out,
right? I'm sorry.
=Just worry about taking care
of yourself.=
=Have you eaten?=
I can still eat.
Did Su Jin stay home from
school?
=Yes.=
Why?
=Well...=
What?
The children heard what their
mothers have said,
and said something to Su Jin.
What did they say?
=That because of Su Jin's father,
other people were suffering.=
=I was really speechless.=
=So I could only say one
word to them.=
=Mom, keep Su Jin home from
school,=
=until I come back.=
Because of you, my son has
passed away.
Because of you, my son is dead!
Just to look for your husband's
corpse,
my healthy son has died!
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
-=Resumption of 2nd Hado
Tunnel project approved
by 65%.=-
-=Consent to restart 2nd Hado
Tunnel project=-
We understand it's very
difficult.
But the longer this drags on,
our situation also becomes
more difficult.
The country also feels it's
time to stop.
More than 65% do.
Everyone is exhausted.
If you keep insisting they
continue,
and someone else gets hurt,
what will you do then?
It's time that you face reality.
But...
Please go ahead.
If my husband is still alive,
then what?
Wouldn't you feel sorry to him?
Stop work!
=Oppa. Oppa, are you
listening?=
=It's Se Hyeon.=
=I don't know if you can still
hear me or not.=
=It must be very cold.=
You must be hungry.
I went to sign papers today.
There's a second tunnel nearby.
I signed the consent for them
to start work again.
They're going to stop...
trying to save you.
=Everyone has to leave now.=
=The rescue effort is over.=
=Stop waiting.=
=Nobody will be coming.=
=I know I shouldn't say that.=
=I'm sorry.=
=It's a terrible thing to have
to say.=
Maybe... Maybe you're not
still waiting.
I was afraid you might keep
waiting for us and not leave.
I'm sorry, Oppa.
=But are you still alive?=
The people here have said you
couldn't still be in this world.
They say that you're dead.
=I'm sorry, Oppa.=
But if you're listening to me
right now, what will we do?
Oppa, I'm really sorry.
I'm sorry, Oppa.
Oppa. Jeong Su oppa.
I'm sorry.
What should I do?
They can't.
I'm still alive.
I'm alive.
After an interruption of 27 days
due to rescue efforts for Lee
Jeong Su,
After an interruption of 27 days
due to rescue efforts for Lee
Jeong Su,
the second Hado Tunnel project
will be restarting today.
After completion of the 2nd
tunnel, the drive from Hado to
Seoul
will be less than 40 minutes.
Captain, if you take this upon
yourself, I'll get fired.
The channel has been in there
too long.
It might be bent or even have
a crack.
This is very dangerous, Captain.
You don't have to do this.
I told him to wait.
I would be despicable if I
just walked away now.
Whether he's alive or dead,
I have to be sure.
Send me down.
Stay in contact with us.
If anything goes wrong, I'm
pulling you up immediately.
Okay.
=You'll be there soon.=
=There may be some vibrations.=
=Hold on tightly.=
You could have told me sooner.
Drilling leader! Who is it?
Did they go down?
He wanted to make a
final confirmation.
Pull him back up right now!
They're about to start blasting!
=Captain. Captain?=
Drilling leader, don't talk to me.
It's too noisy.
=I'm sorry, but you have to
come up right now.=
Wait! Just give me 5 minutes!
=Close the door. I'm pulling
you up right now.=
Lee Jeong Su! Lee Jeong Su!
Lee Jeong Su!
Is it all clear now?
Do you know how expensive
this is?
There are only a few of these
in the country!
That's enough already!
You should just care more
about the equipment.
Wait!
Why?
Stop! Stop working!
Nobody move!
Don't you move! Don't move!
Don't move! Stop!
There's movement!
Demolition team! Demolition team!
Stop blasting! Stop blasting!
Lee Jeong Su is still alive!
Stop blasting!
-=35 days after collapse=-
Captain, over there.
He's coming out!
Lee Jeong Su, how are you
feeling?
Please clear the way!
I'm sorry!
Please move aside!
Clear the way! Move aside!
Hey. Why aren't we going?
They want us to wait a moment.
Who said that? Why?
Just a moment.
The Minister is coming.
Wait a moment longer
before you go.
Are you out of your mind?
Take it up with the Department.
She's here right now.
Minister, please say something!
Wait! It looks like Lee Jeong
Su is saying something!
What are his first words after
coming back into the world?
What did he say?
Please tell us what he said!
We can't hear you!
Say it louder!
Okay.
"Tell those sons of bitches
to get lost!"
That's what he said.
Okay. Take him away.
Lift. 1. 2. 3.
Who did he mean? Me? Why?
After being buried for 35 days,
Lee Jeong Su has come back
safely.
For a person buried alone,
this has special significance as
the world's record.
But before we rejoice, there
were some big problems with
the rescue efforts.
But before we rejoice, there
were some big problems with
the rescue efforts.
He gave a thumbs up to thank
the government for their efforts.
Once again, we are all grateful
to the government and the
nation for the rescue efforts.
Once again, we are all grateful
to the government and the
nation for the rescue efforts.
The events of today have
reminded me that there is
nothing in this whole world
The events of today have
reminded me that there is
nothing in this whole world
The events of today have
reminded me that there is
nothing in this whole world
The events of today have
reminded me that there is
nothing in this whole world
more important than even
one person's life.
How can you park your car here?
I should not have used profanity,
as it undermines the reputation
of civil servants.
Why should I have to write this?
They asked me what he said
and I just told them.
So why should I have to write
a letter of apology?
They all deserved it anyway.
Shostakovich.
=We were just listening to
Shostakovich.=
=Violin Concerto No. 1.=
If I had stayed any longer,
I could have written a symphony.
=He's finally going home after
a long time.=
=We hope he can finally eat and
make up for everything he
missed.=
=Su Jin, you must go to bed
early tonight.=
=Lee Jeong Su, to help your
strength today,=
=we will play an energizing
song for you.=
This guy is too funny.
Wouldn't he get fired for
saying things like that?
My mother made braised pork
ribs. Does that sound good?
Really good.
=Tunnel ahead. Please drive
safely.=