The Truth Beneath / There's No Secret
Former anchor prominent young candidates Korea, Kim Jong Chan.
Plus, there is still a formidable opponent.
No candidate Soon Jae-gu Sinseong party re-elected for the fourth time.
History proves if the ruling party is always far more dominant in terms of number of votes.
Will the election of all 21 this year,
a change of generation or authorities,
take a hold of people.
- You guys have been working hard. - Good, good.
You've arrived? Welcome.
Come in, please sign in.
Welcome!
Aigoo, look who it is!
thanks.
The members of the Council, this is my mother.
Aigoo Eomoni, good to see you.
No Jae Soon
Come on, please have a seat.
Father, again No. Jae Soon the phone.
It's truly endless.
Min Jin.
Why can last working for 16 years under the old fart No?
People who have worked with me for 16 years suddenly flip
This is the low standard of our village council members. Beware of people like this, Jong Chan.
Yeonggam-nim, we've heard rumblings if every morning you wake Candidate Kim by phone.
It is true.
Who is this?
It's okay, I use a speaker phone so that others also follow the hearing, Seonbae-nim.
Hello, Board Member No.
Halo!
Eomma, today I'm going home tonight.
Oh, yes? You said today you will go home tonight?
I have to complete the task of art.
My face!
I work together with Hye Ja.
I know from today Eomma Appa will be very busy.
At moments like this I will be more careful.
Write the phone number Hye Ja and paste it into a memo board!
My granddaughter loved ones.
This year's birthday gift like any of Halmeoni?
Eomoni, no. No need to prepare anything.
At my birthday, I'd love a hundred million Won, Halmeoni.
Incidentally I've been preparing for a birthday party for him.
You're definitely going to win.
During this so finished asking Korea Party candidate, Daesan eleksi always announce the results early.
Because it was here never held any campaign activities.
But there is little change of the circumstances here this year.
Let's examine the eastern region Sinseong-gu Daesan this.
Due to the well-known former anchor Candidate Kim Jong Chan, this area
unexpectedly by many people, getting a lot of attention.
In Sinseong-gu is also Member of the Board No Jae Soon of Korea Party previously been successful in several previous elections.
Results nomination Korea this time gives new breakthroughs as predicted people.
Public opinion stating that if strategy propaganda campaign launch Candidate Kim Jong Chan was very successful.
Candidate No. 1, Kim Jong Chan.
Aigoo, really thank you.
The new political system, supporting Kim Jong Chan!
Candidate No. 1, Kim Jong Chan!
The new generation, support Kim Jong Chan!
The phone number you're going, temporarily unable to be contacted.
You will be redirected to voicemail. Leave your message after the following sound.
I told you a wrong number.
I told you a wrong number. Ja Hye
Hye Ja ... Maybe you know a person named Hye Ja's?
I do not know. The person named Hye Ja and the wealth.
Mother Min Jin
Ms. Min Jin
Five, four, three, two, one.
Five, four, three, two, one. - Not here. I told you not here.
He is not here. There are already more than a year we have not met.
She was with her boyfriend tuh!
Hye Ja? Hye Ja ...
Ja Hye? Do not know right!
Halo?
Yeobo, there was a bit of a problem.
Min Jin until now still not home.
Aigoo ...
Unwrapped turned out to be the wife of a candidate Kim Jong Chan is the Jeolla-do. Why Candidate Kim Jong Chan had to hide his wife's hometown?
No. Jae Soon on the homepage seems so smug.
Unwrapped candidate turns out the wife of Kim Jong Chan is the Jeolla-do. Why Candidate Kim Jong Chan had to hide his wife's hometown?
If directly to the police now, and his son was home alone,
there is the possibility of causing negative rumors spread.
It could be make headache alone.
Min Jin running away from home is also not the first time.
Three months later there is no event like this.
Due to what will be caused by this controversy, the movements of the two candidates currently in the spotlight masses.
Women's sexy night club proved to be a single teenage daughter of a parliamentary candidate who is also a well-known former news anchor.
Why, really flirty gorgeous children.
Judging from these photos, is really a very interesting child.
It seems a bit outrageous to call a small child as flirtatious.
Do you hear it?
Of course! Which may not? I'm not deaf.
All these are photographs of two years ago.
Do not know why it's time Min Jin quarreled with his friend.
Schoolmate take photos secretly to the complaint to the guidance counselor. It happened too long.
Where can from these photos?
True you from Jeolla-do?
Out err what?
Smile a little, jesu-ssi.
[Jesu - brother-in-law]
Come out for a while!
Iya tuh! Smile a little.
Promised me ...
... Will not be so again.
But the phone number was wrong numbers Hye Ja.
Hape Min Jin also inactive continue.
After all, you were ...
Why should hide her hometown?
It was like being stabbed in the back.
It was clear out a problem like this is very sensitive.
Who stab you from behind?
Yes you gone mad?
Why do we have to announce it like this before?
What? - What do you want?
Why are you so hot?
Not me hot.
Now this is an odd sounding spiel seonbae.
Hey, fuck you!
All the things that are here,
I'm the one who took the decision.
You bastard!
This campaign is yours what?
I'm also not so sure. But try to be patient Min Jin see how it goes.
Must protect our children.
This is your main strategy.
Wait a day longer.
Can not! Time to leave school Min Jin did not bring an umbrella.
If because of this problem we lose, you do not mind?
Child runs away from home will not make you lose.
Seriously do. Do not underestimate Yeonggam.
As soon as she got to know our secret, no one knows what it will do.
Should be considered carefully.
True, later also will surely go home alone.
The image of our daughter is also important.
What the heck should worry about?
Party of Korea is not the main target of a political career.
There is a saying of the Jeolla-do.
Although seriously ill until unconscious, the evening still had to be filled with the passion of love.
This means that if a child to death, elderly people live to make another one.
Dead child, but parents will not die.
I will try all my might to raise the Party of Korea.
If it is destined to be finished, just change the other.
If the news you work with people to get caught, they would be very angry.
Really does nothing?
Do not dither! The battlefield must be met with a smile.
Forming a new party, you're able to let go of the position as a daepyo?
[Daepyo - representative]
Ja Hye 010-6762-2171
His name is Hye Ja, Ja Hye.
Hye Ja?
It is not clear what his clan. Grades 3-11.
Height almost equal to Min Jin.
His father was a civil servant.
If no one he wears glasses and leopard motifs have long legs.
Her hair was always disheveled.
And very smart in terms of art.
You ever meet him?
He said a good friend?
Never met directly or touch by phone
Hye Ja's the same man.
Not only know if he was a brilliant academic value.
Do you know anyone named Baek Ok Soon this?
Hye Ja phone number that you said it,
is the phone number Baek Ok Soon.
Residence in Gyeonggi-do.
Do not know her. Do not know who this person is.
The wife of Kim Jong Chan candidate of the Party of Korea Uncovered came from Jeolla-do. Father-in-law came from Jeolla-do and the Gwangju civil servants. Kim Jong Chan deliberately hide this fact.
Phone numbers of children
former friends my playmate.
Everything is not a good girl.
Perhaps this data can help you.
Hit and run incident last night but there was no other incident.
Where the scene?
On the outside of the roundabout near the U-Town.
Involved was a man. After all he is a newcomer.
Maybe ... you know a woman named Choi Mi Ok?
- Choi Mi Ok? - Really.
No.
Can record the call?
People who are the highest intensity of communication with Min Jin Hye Ja but not this friend.
His name is Choi Mi Ok, female school student junior class Sinseong 3-7.
Never met him.
Anu, something happens to Min Jin?
Height almost equal to Min Jin.
Wearing glasses leopard motif.
Length of her legs, the hair is always a mess.
His father was a civil servant. You said, 'right?
Kim Yeon Hong
No, he never said if Ja Hye very good in the field of art.
I do not understand art, Yeobo.
If so, try Hye Ja says that's who.
Really sorry.
The name of this Hye Ja ...
... Absolutely not in school Min Jin.
Also no child posture of medium height and his father was a civil servant.
Yesterday Min Jin also no art classes.
Yeah, Min Jin no art class yesterday.
Signal HAPE Min Jin
in the afternoon about 4:15 o'clock two days ago disappeared.
Its location is the school.
Hours segitu was no art class.
Possible hapenya exhausted betere also very high.
He is Choi Mi Ok.
Yesterday Min Jin and Choi Mi Ok was in school until the evening.
Because he does not bring an umbrella.
Choi Mi Ok (16)
Yesterday I and Min Jin long been at the new school home.
From behind heard no engine noise car, so I'm turning my head and see.
He left on the car. White sedan.
Do not lie! Not maybe my son carelessly climbed into a stranger.
It looks like the two of them know each other.
Boys or girls?
It looks like the guy, but what I like girls too huh?
I do not remember the license plate number.
All CCTV in the area around it has been checked.
But there was nothing.
What does your father do?
A driver.
Trucks taIk. One truck contents taIk all.
It's called sludge trucks.
Continue your mother?
Do not have a mother, their stepmother.
A family of three of them live at home?
Halmeoni also exist. Her health condition is very bad.
Continue to have two younger sisters and two younger brothers.
Can think of where this?
You know what this stuff?
Watch.
Your father brought the truck fecal feed 8 people,
You say this is yours?
This is a man to his father Min Jin.
Used by Min Jin after he replaced his watch strap.
She said after moving here stolen.
Because the price is very expensive, I did not dare to tell the police and you say this is yours?
Damn! This is mine!
Search for a missing child
Wanted missing children
Choi Mi Ok? Schoolgirl Choi Mi Ok?
Search for a missing child
Mau was a cop or a reporter,
Want the police or reporters
Kim Chang Hoon (32)
a student asked me about that one.
Because I was homeroom Min Jin.
Kim Chang Hoon (32)
Yes, true.
Last year I had become homeroom Choi Mi Ok.
Eom Ok Ran (41)
But just now the police have a check.
Student academic achievement is quite remarkable.
Can be considered stable.
Min Jin Mi Ok and two students have had a close relationship.
First grade they had been classmates.
But Seonsaeng-nim, you're obviously lying.
You said a stable academic grades are not up and down.
It is clearly up and down.
There is no evidence that if the boy had stolen a watch Min Jin.
Tell the police could so carelessly will involve many people.
Silence, the child will not be back.
How good is it?
I know in a situation like this will seem a bit silly I said like this.
You remember in high school we've made arrangements regarding the dream of the future?
Sure, you say you want to be like Hillary (Clinton) to be a mother country.
If I either gone mad or anything, I said I wanted to be a wife and a good mother.
Yeon Hong us at that time pretty incredible.
By the way, where Min Jin is?
Already, halo?
Have arrived.
I am from the Crime Unit.
- In the future both cases the loss of your daughter will be handled by me. - Let's talk in the car alone.
The loss of your daughter are both first noticed by Samunim.
Really.
That day is the first day of the campaign.
What is the reason Candidate Kim continue to participate in campaigning even though her daughter is missing?
The level of support obtained should be getting dropped, is not it?
You expect me to not participate in the election?
No, it's just that there is a bit of a question mark.
There was a smell of feces, needed fresh air.
By the time your daughter is gone, what are you doing?
What did you say?
At that time there was a very important meeting.
Who are the participants of the meeting?
It can not be kukomentari for political reasons.
Just tell them, Yeobo.
Later in time if it is necessary, just let me tell you.
Remembering all the times where you rebelled and was determined to become a singer.
About genes inherited by the daughter who we are? Every day make him just a storm in the outdoor.
Of course he is hiding where.
Just lost your daughter could not be found.
That day you were drinking with anyone until late so?
Important is this issue?
This is a serious problem.
How important?
This issue relates to the decision to live with you,
or enough to stay here.
What?
If anything happens to themselves Min Jin,
what would you do?
Our daughter is missing!
As a father the whole brain just met how to win in the election!
As this son can have the desire to go home?
The people I meet are the ones who can you trust.
The way you like it before you want me to say?
Love being able to serve you. How may I help you?
Hello, my name is Kim Min Jin.
I forgot his password, what should I do?
Tell a password. Dear visitor, below are details of the search password
Manual search password. Accounts: whRkwhRk, password: rlaalswlsWkd
Jo-jo-kka kka .. ..
[Input Korean keyboard whRkwhRk  jo-jo-kka kka which literally means 'fuck']
[Input keyboard Korea rlaalswlsWkd  Kim Min Jin Jjang]
E-mail unread No 53 660.
Why not cleaned, Min Jin.
Joo Seong Rim-"How Min Jin? Long time no see.
Looking for a sexual partner
My daughter Kim Min Jin will definitely be back.
I, Kim Jong Chan will never collapse.
At the time my daughter back,
I'll make it look not the least bit wobbly!
The attitude of a father who never left his political duties.
Kim Jong Chan! Kim Jong Chan!
Kim Jong Chan!
Already, halo?
Sorry, disrupting the morning.
I'm the mother of Kim Min Jin Sinseong junior high school student.
Yes, Eomonim.
Speech need not so shy.
We occasionally touch by phone.
The start of the current class.
So the police have also been here.
Today ... is a day where Min Jin lost.
Oh, it was the day piketku.
Starting this month I started there to picket.
After seeing this maybe you will understand.
The audience does not look very enthusiastic about their stage performance.
It looks like you did not know.
Min Jin ostracized by her friends.
He says at least willing, if after his mother knew he would feel sad.
Day...
... Also are outcasts.
I should find time to inform you.
I was also very worried. Therefore...
Help me, Seonsaeng-nim.
Eomonim.
Today it was fitting when making kimbap had scooped a few pieces for her, after that I never saw him again.
I also do not know if Min Jin now eat on time or not.
Help me.
I'm sorry, homonym.
I know all this already.
Please help me, Seonsaeng-nim.
My daughter is gone, but nothing has changed at all.
There is only one.
No. Jae Soon the phone every morning is not a phone anymore.
Petunjuk Kandidat No Jae Soon
nothing to do with the loss of your daughter has not been found.
I knew it would be like this.
I can not, can not be like this.
Please show me all the data penyidikanmu!
Ini adalah tindakan yang ilegal, Samunim.
When doing this, it could be I have to take off my uniform.
By doing so, Kim candidate makes no difference to have violated the law.
You will give voice to the No. Jae Soon, right?
No. Jae Soon, if left alone ...
not going to happen to my daughter?
I'm going to a place, come with me.
Samunim, if you so continue to be difficult for my position.
Good, now try to focus your eyes on one point.
Inhale deeply and then exhale slowly.
It was blinding. Pull another deep breath.
There was parked a white sedan car.
There is a Ajumma talking to Min Jin.
Ajumma that her hair braided.
His face was quite beautiful.
Seoul dialect.
About what time?
I do not know.
Car number plate, it can seem to you?
Invisible.
Oh, yes? Then we go back again
to the first time you saw that car.
The car was speeding past me.
Instead, the car drove by slowly.
Drove very slowly.
1... 8... Geo..
8..5 ... look no further.
The road to where? Min Jin her.
Seoul.
To Seoul? What are you doing?
Being a singer.
Hey, Min Jin said he wanted to Seoul?
He has?
Did not you say he was going to Seoul to become a singer?
Indeed there I say so?
Are you sure he hypnotized?
Want to try again?
Do not waste time on things that are not useful.
Enough already!
Noisy!
No. 5 No. Jae Soon!
Secretary General Park (45)
Already inside, right?
Where the last schedule Candidate Kim first night campaign?
The day was busy until the early hours of 2.
After he came home I was not clear where he went to.
Candidate Kim last schedule in the evening the first campaign?
Of course I took her home. Wait a minute, please.
Driver Choi (46)
Hotel Regency Sinseong.
Hotel? Segitu hours drinking there?
With whom?
People who met him seems to be a Board Member of Sin Seon Mi
After that they went both of them. Should still not possible mistaken.
By the way, the arms wound Samonim how?
Why? Want me to check, Samonim?
There is a possibility really do not know.
Never mind. 16-year-old man along with the No Jae Soon.
None of the people here who should be trusted.
Why should the hell are you? Make worried people.
Anyway, do not worry.
Help me one thing. Please show me the data of the police investigation on Ji Min's case.
It can not. Data investigation ...
by law it is illegal to be opened to the public.
16 years ... So long as the followers No Jae Soon.
Connections like this at least there.
Can not ya can not.
It is a violation of the Personal Information Protection Law
Maaf, Samunim.
Last time I want to ask.
That night ...
Jin Min's father met with whom you did not know?
Iya, aku sama sekali tidak tahu Samunim.
Bring investigative data Min Jin me!
If you've betrayed and defected No Jae Soon here,
at least you have to prove to us if you are the one who can we trust.
Do not just want riches to live your life.
Yes Secretary General, I will be watching Samunim well. Do not worry.
Study examine carefully ... carefully. Keep your brain in order to keep a clear head.
Examine carefully ... think carefully.
Keep your brain in order to keep a clear head. Examine carefully.
The review more closely starting from scratch.
That day is the first day of my husband's campaign.
I also campaign issue due to busy, no time for anything else.
I made my daughter eat kimbap. Is she eating properly?
Oh yes, that day ... that day ...
I heard that song often sung by Min Jin.
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10.
Then 11.
Do you have any evidence if the day was No. Jae Soon whistling in front of you?
Moreover, you have proof if the song is a love song sung Min Jin?
We tapped! I suspected as No. Jae Soon Gregg's ...
That's why he could know the song often sung Min Jin.
Pick up all the equipment we have in No. Jae Soon and replace it with this.
Immediately remove from office Yeonggam.
Kim Min Jin, Kim Yeon Hong, Kim Jong Chan
Daughter Kim Jong Chan candidate of the Party of Korea
to this day has been missing for 10 days.
Sinseong-gu, the amount of support the independent candidate No. Jae Soon occupy exceptional advantages.
Kim Jong Chan candidate who does not care
whereabouts of her daughter and remain actively involved in this election,
Candidate Kim Jong Chan, step back!
To be able to get sympathy from supporters who already disappointed
Seems to be a very difficult mission.
seems to be a very difficult mission.
What do you want?
Save your daughter?
All of Jeolla-do, get out of here!
Or help your husband?
Please save my daughter ... Please save my daughter.
As a mother, so incompetent.
Still dare rear its head?
Please save my daughter ... Please save my daughter.
Use your heart to move the gods! Use your heart to move the gods!
Kim Min Jin 1999.10 ~ 2014.10 Until we meet in heaven, my daughter who I love most.
Wiwonjang Jong Moo Hyun of Korea Party
[Wiwonjang - equivalent to the post of governor]
Choi Moon Sik Dojisa,
[Dojisa - Governor]
and Park Jong Un Sijang of Daesansi attended the funeral.
[Sijang - mayor]
All members of the city council is also present.
Independent candidates Sinseong-gu, No. Jae Soon
Candidates along with Ja Cheol Hee also present.
Moon Wiwonjang personally attended the funeral.
Public Opinion sure if this is a form of support for the candidate Kim Jong Chan to finish the campaign program.
Why can happen something like this?
Kim Min Jin lost on the day of the commencement of the campaign
eventually returned to the side of his parents in a state of motionless.
Discordant voices that had been cornered Candidate Kim Jong Chan
slowly turned into sympathy and support.
Jin Min's death had saved his father.
At this time all the people mourn the departure of Min Jin.
Bunyi bel berdenting ting ting ting ting ting.
End of the skirt revealed ... a mad woman going carrying garlands. Get out!
10240 ... small meteor falling from the sky in green ...
The hole filled with darkness. The place where you were not illuminated by sunlight. Only darkness.
- Gila!
- Yeobo! Yeobo!
At that time I felt no matter what I say,
you will never forgive me.
Actually, today it is Sin Seon Mi Board Member of Sejong party.
I know.
Surely while drinking alcohol thrash out great promise in the future.
We are already over.
Yeobo ...
Do not tell me over.
We are already over.
You and I can not be over just like that.
Want it atupun electoral politics, had no meaning anymore.
You! Who killed my son.
Please ... please so you calm down and think again.
Settle down and think again?
Honestly, I believe it may be
Secretary General to have the sympathy of the people and killed my daughter.
Or you can for the sake of winning this election
paying people to kill my daughter.
Under the covers, anyone can not be trusted.
The brains of people who are here there is only political.
Points depraved morals!
Enya!
Have you forgotten? Have you forgotten what ever you say?
My daughter really died for me.
So I have nothing, Yeobo?
10240.
10240... 10240...
10240...
Bunyi bel berdenting ting ting ting ting ting.
End of the skirt revealed ... a crazy woman ...
go carrying garlands. Get out!
Small meteors falling from the sky in green ...
The hole filled with darkness.
The place where you were not illuminated by sunlight. Only darkness.
No smell of cigarettes on you. You are my food, cemilanku, my soul.
10240.
You can correct the overall winner?
Min Jin academic value every time there must be progress.
Although it feels strange, but I want to believe it.
The sound of the bell tinkled .. Ting, ting, ting, ting, ting.
Fringe skirt revealed .. crazy woman came out carrying flowers. Get out!
Enyah!
Small meteor falling from the sky is green ..
The hole filled with darkness. The place where you were not illuminated by sunlight. Only darkness.
10240..
Seonsaeng-nim, what your email?
There is something I want to send it to you.
I'm a little busy right now.
Soon should I call?
This is my email account.
Choi Mi Ok is suspect?
In the evenings where Min Jin missing,
there are witnesses who saw Mi Ok passing with bodies covered in blood.
Eomonim, certainly Mi Ok maybe not do that.
SMS was already entered. Thanks, Seonsaeng-nim.
Even if you did not commit.
But if it was not you who killed,
why is there blood in the sports shoe yours?
Why do not you see! No visible black spots this?
It is the blood of Min Jin, Jin Min blood.
DNA test results show this is the blood of Min Jin.
That's why I suggested a not lie.
Before once me and Min Jin moving goods.
At that time there was a taxi ran a red light and drove toward us.
I encourage Min Jin like this.
Min Jin fell and scraped her knee.
Blood stains on the sports shoe is derived from that day.
Eomoni!
Skirt school uniform belonged to Min Jin!
So short, his butt almost invisible.
You said scraped knee injury. You think I can not know if there are things like this?
You do not lie!
It is true that there are abrasions on knees Min Jin.
But the wounding of when, not yet certain.
Therefore, calm yourself first.
When to scratch?
Eomonim!
My daughter is not the culprit.
Help out first!
Driver Choi ... is her father?
What is this? From the beginning you already know?
Out .. out first.
Your daughter ... my husband called feces.
He said the car driven by his father, was filled with feces!
Son, why talk like that?
It is definitely time at home driver Choi talk like that.
So much hate you to my husband?
My daughter!
not an ordinary child talk like that. - Come out first.
I did not teach him anything. Also very excellent academic value.
It's a very good boy.
The daughter of a truck driver faeces which may be a good academic grades?
Two years ago your daughter
academic grades are not the result of his hard work.
Ask yourself on your daughter.
- What happened exactly? - Detective Lee.
If you've finished, please go.
As a father, at least the child's academic progress note. A little strange, is not it?
You're fired!
Asshole!
Stop!
According to rumors, residence and work space Candidate Kim Jong Chan tapped illegally,
on the instructions of Candidates No. Jae Soon.
Here is the response from independent candidate No. Jae Soon.
Kandidat Kim Jong Chan...
use the cases of illegal tapping is still not certain truth
I accidentally scapegoat in the middle of the campaign.
I assure you that by using my political career, I would have to uncover the truth.
After the death of Min Jin
my husband's position in this election is very advantageous.
Secretary General...
managed to help me get the investigation report the case of Min Jin.
There was a child dressed in the uniform of there
walk here without opening the umbrella.
Like the ghost of a woman.
I got to thinking the rain was so heavy why he was so.
It turns out the boy's entire body was covered in blood.
Body also filled with mud.
Then I asked him why not come home even in the rain.
Why not go home even in the rain?
But the boy ran away.
But, it was raining too hard,
plus the sky was dark. The boy was the establishment far away from me.
So, the child is a child who was ...
or not the child who was ...
It seems not.
No, he's not Mi Ok.
- Not. - Interrogation ended.
On the uniform Choi Mi Ok, there were no blood stains.
What color is this?
Trying to give a different answer to his conscience.
Green color.
Well, starting now yes.
Your father is a driver's father Min Jin,
hurt your pride?
No.
You ... bury Min Jin?
Why hapemu reformatted?
Anyone want you hiding?
Today it is exposed to rain so problematic.
Just answer with a 'yes' or 'no'.
Because it was reformatted.
Min Jin did you kill?
No.
Min Jin ...
was the son of the hated person.
When her father came to school to become a teacher one day
friends the other must also have the same feelings.
His father ya?
Ajussi how your income?
There is as much as my father?
I understand your feeling.
This is our secret. I promise.
Why? You're not willing to work as an anchor woman?
If you want to become an anchor woman, what should I do?
Sorry.
Because I had spent some time in Washington joined my father.
You mad?
Do not be angry.
Enyah!
Gab: The job has been completed correctly? When will the new picture given? 10:27 Morning 3:20.
Really dumb.
Can not die.
At the hospital feeling quite ugly.
It may be that later had to receive psychiatric treatment.
Wah! Do you like the songs of Joan Faye ya?
Joan Faye!
Name the song Wild Rose Hill, okay?
Want to teach you a way that is really effective?
Really effective way is to jump down from the top.
Scorching hot.
Note Investigating Murders Candidates daughter Kim Jong Chan.
In the email account for my daughter
mail more than five thousand.
From among that I find the mail received about 2 years ago.
The first semester of the class before the final exam.
Emails received three days earlier.
Take a look here, 10240 send exam questions.
Fill the empty mail.
Lest already sent repeatedly.
Because the content is lost, so resubmitted again.
So my daughter could not remove it.
This is a report card that grades my daughter ever before.
Take a look here!
Starting from the first semester final exam grade one,
value suddenly becomes nice all.
Similarly, Choi Mi Ok.
During that period it ranked second child suddenly developed.
After that stable continues to be in the top ranking.
But Choi Mi Ok now one of the suspects.
You do not feel anything strange?
It is not clear also.
If the rank down about 30 rank is likely to be a problem.
But instead, most people will not feel if this was odd.
My daughter it made no difference to me.
No talent in the field of learning.
Really?
Lest you have a suspicion if the death of Min Jin nothing to do with this.
What's your excuse leaked exam questions to my daughter?
I leaked it because I like it.
Because of that my daughter was murdered?
Yes you crazy?
Why should I kill him?
I really ... really like Min Jin.
If you like it rightly guided him to choose the right path.
Why even give the exam?
Because he wants so.
I only gave exam questions.
The answers to the questions that everything he's working on his own.
Eomoni probably do not know.
Min Jin much smarter than people expected.
If handed over to the police for investigation,
Ji Min for the deceased will only embarrass him alone.
In this election, you can also expect to win, right?
Min Jin in school are often ostracized.
After he died, they also have to be tortured by various rumors, so?
Hit and run incident last night but there was no other incident.
Where the scene?
On the outside of the roundabout near the U-Town.
Involved was a man. After all he is a newcomer.
Do not move! If moving the wound gets worse.
Reported if the main actors persecutor wife Candidates from the party Kim Jong Chan Korea
No candidate is a staunch advocate Jae Soon,
volunteers cleaning the city, Kim XX.
Kim XX previously known to have posted more than 20 articles on the homepage Candidates No. Jae Soon
which vilify princess Candidate Kim Jong Chan and his wife's hometown.
Samunim sudah sadarkan diri.
You assign the Secretary General to send people to watch me, right?
I'm afraid if something happens to you.
This is the latest models.
You should always take it as well.
Also took out the manuals.
Do not get hurt, Yeobo.
Min Jin also would expect if you were okay.
Thanks, Yeobo.
Yeobo, our daughter may not be as good as we think.
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10, 11.
There are still 11 and a half.
Now, our party will begin.
Leisure time in October.
Our future will always be together ...
The darkness of night had arrived.
Times where the stars will be shining brightly.
Syulu lu lu lu lu ... penggal kepalaku.
Syulu lu lu lu lu ... merangkul erat hatiku.
It's time to leave, to the Wild Rose Hill.
Syulu lu lu lu lu ... Tempat di mana kupu-kupu terbang menuju langit.
Yulu lu lu lu lu ... Bless me so that my dream turned into reality.
It's time to leave, to the Wild Rose Hill.
This really is me.
Beginning so fans because they watch the show.
Why?
The lyrics of their songs that really tell my story.
Want video I show Ok Jin and the others?
It is my record.
It certainly Mi Ok would never do anything like that at Min Jin.
Ok adalah orang yang terkeren pernah to jumpai.
We were very happy.
Min Jin was very worried when after his victory in the election he will study abroad and Mi Ok alone would be ostracized here.
If you do not want to be isolated, academic achievement has to be bright
Ways must also be fashionable dress.
Mi Ok family is really poor.
Choi Mi Ok...
For So Yeon.
So Yeon Cho, his style that you like wearing uniforms that are too small like this?
Wild Rose Hill
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10, 11.
Still there are 11 and a half.
Now, our party will begin.
Free time in October.
We are the future will always be together ..
The heart that is being bemoaned.
Later will not be deterred in the least.
Syulu lu lu lu lu ... merangkul erat hatiku.
Embracing close to my heart.
Syulu lu lu lu lu ... penggal kepalaku.
Term head.
Lu lu lu lu Yulu ... Bless me so that my dream turned into reality.
Bless me so that my dream turned into reality.
Leisure time in October.
What you mean is the first day of campaigning dad, right?
The day was very busy father and mother.
Wild Rose Hill is a hill canker.
What is meant by 11 and a half is ...
Tonight at 11:30, right?
One hundred million stars is what?
Money?
Because Min Jin never ask for 100 million as a birthday gift.
You are preparing for a party, is not it?
What party is it?
The intended party is ...
Prepare money for the person who leaked exam questions to you.
I knew who it was.
Min Jin wrote the lyrics I compose the melody.
We will never plagiarized a song written by someone else.
This is your shirt.
Yesterday I met Cho So Yeon.
He was wearing clothes.
You may have already washed many times.
But once checked, will be caught.
My mother has passed away. I only have a father.
But the father is married to the new mother.
Endlessly birth siblings.
At my side there is only Min Jin.
Why should I kill him? Why?
Okay, you did not commit.
And who on earth
Min Jin who killed it?
That girl.
The woman hired someone to kill Min Jin.
This is a killer phone belongs Min Jin.
Problem have you clean up? When are you going to send me a picture?
Take a look here, his name is Gab.
There continues to be a phone number of the mastermind.
Min Jin died because of me.
Because of the money that was willing to be given to me.
Due to a poor family.
And Min Jin will study abroad.
I brought the damn car.
By the time he was off guard.
As did the bastard of Min Jin, I'm over it.
I've learned from my father's driving.
Back and forth back and forth.
One time...
Twice...
Three times...
Addressed to the President.
After Min Jin die, I do not know when I will die.
That's why I'm writing a will.
Mr. President ...
Perpetrators of the murder of Min Jin and I
is the Son So Ra-nim Seonsaeng Princess Sinseong junior high school teacher.
The reason Son So Ra killing us is
because in our hands there is a video she made love with a man.
Last year we gave an air deodorizer that is equipped with a hidden camera in the Son So Ra and secretly recording the video.
Because the woman was
during these two years to help us steal the exam questions.
Finally, after we extort money from her 100 million
She hired people to kill Min Jin.
Dear Mr. President,
please drop the death penalty in Son Seonsaeng So Ra-nim.
It is our hope the last.
May you always in good health.
Signed, Choi Mi Ok.
Restore hapenya me when it's over.
No!
No, give it back to me!
I'm not yet senile.
I just pretended not to know the academic achievement of my daughter.
Not really do not know.
Quick return to me!
Although it is difficult to be believed,
no matter what people want to say,
I really never liked this place.
Since this is the birthplace of my husband.
And the place where my daughter passed her childhood.
This is the order of Kim Yeon Hong.
Confirmation of booking.Happy birthday to-16 Min Jin dear. My daughter Min Jin, really loves. My daughter who is most dear. Mother father.
Min Jin, we are very, very loved.Mom, Dad
You have made a very funny joke.
My friend is dead, but the video was still in my hand.
Gab: Let's meet face to face.
Congressional elections 21st
will soon be started at the same time
for 13,479 voters.
Voting time is from 6 am to 6 pm.
Along with the end of voting time, counting will begin.
They will vote required to carry ID cards, passport, or driver's license.
Elections in all regions will be supervised by the Central Election Commission.
Actors who kill not the No. Min Jin Jae Soon, Yeobo.
But you still insist if all these are deeds No. Jae Soon.
No accused of killing Jae Soon our daughter,
and broke a rib wife.
Do not feel guilty at Min Jin.
Today you have to beat No. Jae Soon.
1. The Party of Korea, Kim Jong Chan.
I tell you the devil would like aia your daughter?
There is only one fault.
But something tells me all of this will never be finished.
It's you, women curse!
Asshole! No matter how remorse is no way back again. Every day I would remind you of this.
Gave birth to a child exactly like you. Women's curse! Basic women's Curse!
In time I will tell him what his mother rubbish like that.
Prostitutes curse!
I'll make you regret having children of your body that dirty!
Bitch shameless!
Kim Jong Chan and homeroom?
I'm not so sure. Looks like hell for the happiness of children.
Do you know?
Your father is the guardian of our class ...
In the man's hand was My videos.
In the man's hand was My videos. Who was the blackmail?
Do not know.In the man's hand was My videos.Who was the blackmail?
Is Jin Min's father hired people to kill Min Jin?
Are you sure?
Why?
Why not tell my husband
if the other party is my daughter?
I hope that the two men were sentenced.
Give me the video!
Look, this is done.
Call my husband now!
People who know about us have been contacted.
Kim Jong Chan, 54.4%
What do you mean? Kan had been cleared.  Kim Jong Chan, 54.4%
What do you mean? Kan had been cleared.
Not one person.
He said that he witnessed the death of his own.
Shit.
I canceled there.
He wants to meet you in person.
Do you know how boring my wife?
Every time during lovemaking,
like a pile of stones, there is absolutely no reaction. At the time of making love ...
Proceed!
Hey! Min Ji is dead! Fucking bastard!
Do not think you're the greatest ass, motherfucker!
There I am! I will replace Min Jin revenge on you, the people of Hell!
If I kill you, means I've lost.
I want you do not want to live, not willing to die.
Yeobo ...
... I managed to beat No. Jae Soon.
Upload video
Candidate Kim Jong Chan along with a female teacher shook mobil.AVI (380MB) | being uploaded.
To my friends who I love most in this world, Mi Ok,Min Jin.
Min Jin!
Min Jin! Min Jin!
You must be very cold.
Must be cold, right?
This Mother, Mother, Min Jin.
My son, it's okay. Nothing.
Do not cry. It's okay, it's okay.
Do not be afraid, do not cry. Nothing.
Do not cry.
Do not cry, do not cry.
My daughter ...
... Ever tell you his mother was like what?
He says you're senile. He says his mother was senile.
So he had to be at your side to protect you.